<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>NATO - Custom Job List</title><link>http://nato.taleo.net/careersection/2/moresearch.ftl?lang=en&amp;jobfield=6270035151</link><description>Custom Job List (Information Communication Technology)</description><item><title>Software Development Engineer  - JAVA </title><link>http://nato.taleo.net/careersection/2/jobdetail.ftl?lang=en&amp;job=251862</link><description>Who we are:&#13;
For more than 70 years, NATO’s mission has been to preserve peace and security in the Alliance for nearly one billion citizens. The NATO Communications and Information Agency (NCI Agency) and its predecessors have worked tirelessly in providing the means that enable the connectedness and togetherness that keep our Alliance strong. We are the NCI Agency, a team of 3000 civilian and military staff in 29 locations throughout Europe, North America and Asia.&#13;
Our technology and cyber ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 10:04:54 EST</pubDate></item><item><title>Data Engineer</title><link>http://nato.taleo.net/careersection/2/jobdetail.ftl?lang=en&amp;job=251926</link><description>Who we are:&#13;
For more than 70 years, NATO’s mission has been to preserve peace and security in the Alliance for nearly one billion citizens. The NATO Communications and Information Agency (NCI Agency) and its predecessors have worked tirelessly in providing the means that enable the connectedness and togetherness that keep our Alliance strong. We are the NCI Agency, a team of 3000 civilian and military staff in 29 locations throughout Europe, North America and Asia.&#13;
Our technology and cyber ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 05:24:34 EST</pubDate></item><item><title>DataOps Technician</title><link>http://nato.taleo.net/careersection/2/jobdetail.ftl?lang=en&amp;job=251704</link><description>1. POST CONTEXT&#13;
This is a position within the Centre for Maritime Research and Experimentation (CMRE), an organization of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO).&#13;
CMRE is an established, world-class scientific research and experimentation facility that organizes and conducts scientific research and technology development, centred on the maritime domain, delivering innovative and field tested Science &amp; Technology (S&amp;T) solutions to address defence and security needs of the Alliance.&#13;
T...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 04:22:41 EST</pubDate></item><item><title>Software Licensing Manager</title><link>http://nato.taleo.net/careersection/2/jobdetail.ftl?lang=en&amp;job=251296</link><description>Who we are:&#13;
For more than 70 years, NATO’s mission has been to preserve peace and security in the Alliance for nearly one billion citizens. The NATO Communications and Information Agency (NCI Agency) and its predecessors have worked tirelessly in providing the means that enable the connectedness and togetherness that keep our Alliance strong. We are the NCI Agency, a team of 3000 civilian and military staff in 29 locations throughout Europe, North America and Asia.&#13;
Our technology and cyber ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 04:12:42 EST</pubDate></item><item><title>Business Analyst</title><link>http://nato.taleo.net/careersection/2/jobdetail.ftl?lang=en&amp;job=251344</link><description>Who we are&#13;
For more than 75 years, NATO’s mission has been to preserve peace and security in the Alliance for nearly one billion citizens. The NATO Communications and Information Agency (NCIA) and its predecessors have worked tirelessly in providing the means that enable the connectedness and togetherness that keep our Alliance strong. We are the NCIA, a team of 3400 civilian and military staff in 29 locations throughout Europe, North America and Asia.&#13;
Our technology and cyber experts allow...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 04:10:33 EST</pubDate></item><item><title> Principal Technician - Air &amp; Maritime Systems</title><link>http://nato.taleo.net/careersection/2/jobdetail.ftl?lang=en&amp;job=251912</link><description>&#13;
&#13;
Who we are:&#13;
For more than 70 years, NATO’s mission has been to preserve peace and security in the Alliance for nearly one billion citizens. The NATO Communications and Information Agency (NCI Agency) and its predecessors have worked tirelessly in providing the means that enable the connectedness and togetherness that keep our Alliance strong. We are the NCI Agency, a team of 3000 civilian and military staff in 29 locations throughout Europe, North America and Asia.&#13;
Our technology and cy...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 08:52:29 EST</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Analysts (Operational Analysis) </title><link>http://nato.taleo.net/careersection/2/jobdetail.ftl?lang=en&amp;job=251857</link><description>&#13;
&#13;
Who we are:&#13;
For more than 70 years, NATO’s mission has been to preserve peace and security in the Alliance for nearly one billion citizens. The NATO Communications and Information Agency (NCIA) and its predecessors have worked tirelessly in providing the means that enable the connectedness and togetherness that keep our Alliance strong. We are the NCIA, a team of over 3000 civilian and military staff in 29 locations throughout Europe, North America and Asia.&#13;
Our technology and cyber exp...</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 09:59:45 EST</pubDate></item><item><title>Temporary Post - CIS Technician</title><link>http://nato.taleo.net/careersection/2/jobdetail.ftl?lang=en&amp;job=251898</link><description>In view of the nature and of the urgency of the temporary positions we are looking to fill, it is important for candidates to be available for temporary employment on short notice. In practice, this implies either being in possession of valid NATO security clearance at the time of application, or having been in possession of such a clearance with the possibility to reactivate it swiftly. Please note that only applicants with a valid NATO security clearance will be considered for selective ass...</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 08:33:57 EST</pubDate></item><item><title>System Administrator</title><link>http://nato.taleo.net/careersection/2/jobdetail.ftl?lang=en&amp;job=251446</link><description>Who we are:&#13;
For 75 years, NATO’s mission has been to preserve peace and security in the Alliance for nearly one billion citizens. The NATO Communications and Information Agency (NCIA) and its predecessors have worked tirelessly in providing the means that enable the connectedness and togetherness that keep our Alliance strong. We are the NCI Agency, a team of 3000 civilian and military staff in 29 locations throughout Europe, North America and Asia.&#13;
Our technology and cyber experts allow NA...</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:07:45 EST</pubDate></item><item><title>Systems Technician</title><link>http://nato.taleo.net/careersection/2/jobdetail.ftl?lang=en&amp;job=251864</link><description>1. SUMMARY&#13;
The BICES Group Executive (BGX), a NATO entity, is the executive body of the BICES Group (BG). The BG exists to enable the sharing and exchange of Intelligence and Information between and amongst the NATO nations, with NATO, and with other non-NATO nations and Organisations. The BGX, under the leadership of the Director, is comprised of the following pillars: Intelligence and Enterprise Services (IES) Division, Programmes, Engineering and Maintenance (PEM) Division, Operations and...</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 10:39:24 EST</pubDate></item><item><title>More Jobs Available on Career Section...</title><link>http://nato.taleo.net/careersection/2/moresearch.ftl?lang=en&amp;jobfield=6270035151</link><description>The system found more than 10 jobs matching the criteria you have selected. Click the link above to return to the Career section and view the remaining jobs.</description></item></channel></rss>